["The Way We Touch"
by We Are Twin playing]
[woman] Demi and I
went to college together.
The right type of guy for her
is someone who is sweet and honest,
but she always falls for the really
good-looking men who are assholes.
♪ You'd be the best
That I ever hoped for ♪
♪ I love it how I can't resist
The way you are ♪
♪ The way we touch... ♪
[woman] I've known Demi
for about three years now.
In New York, Demi just dated
the same kind of guy,
but she's been here in New Orleans
for about a year,
and so she needs to open up her mind set.
♪ If we are a match ♪
♪ I'd give you everything I longed for ♪
♪ I love it how I can't resist
The way you are ♪
♪ The way we touch... ♪
[woman]
Demi always falls for the wrong guys.
I do want her to find love
in somebody that wants her
just as much as she wants them.
♪ The way we touch ♪
Hi.
-Demi?
-Yes.
-And your name is?
-Britton.
-Could you repeat that?
-Britton, nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
Good. Good. Really like your shirt.
-Thank you.
-It's nice.
Yeah. I've been dying to meet you 'cause
I'm like, once I actually meet you,
-I'll relax a little bit.
-Then you'll be fine, I know. [chuckles]
-[Noel] You wanna grab a drink at the bar?
-[Demi] Let's do it. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hello, hello.
-Hi.
-Hi. How's it going?
All right.
What do you--? What do you drink?
I am a big fan of bourbon, to be honest.
-Yes. Yes, for dark.
-Yes.
-[Allan] What's up, how you doing?
-Hi.
-Allan?
-Yes.
-Demi. Nice to meet you. I do hugs.
-Nice to meet you too.
-Oh, good. Latina?
-Hi.
Yes. Are you too?
-Yeah, definitely.
-From where?
Honduras.
-Oh. Dominicana.
-Dominicana?
-Yeah.
-[in Spanish] How nice.
-Are you fluent?
-[in Spanish] In Spanish?
-Of course. I speak perfect Spanish.
-[in English] Yeah. Good.
[in English] Well,
it's definitely nice to meet you.
Cool. Cool.
I... I set up a lot of game nights.
Like, I, people, like--
Okay, so, I'm really into board games.
[laughs]
-So...
-Same here.
-Yeah?
-I love game nights.
Back in New York,
my house was the house to go to.
-Right.
-Jenga, like, I would write on the blocks.
That's the fun one. Do you Giant Jenga?
-I have Giant Jenga.
-No. I lived in a New York City apartment.
Giant Jenga would've been,
like, my chandelier.
-I can't do all of that.
-Yeah.
But I love game nights.
[laughing]
I'll have a vodka with pineapple
-and like a splash of cranberry.
-Ah, la piña.
I'm gonna do the... the Tommy's Margarita.
-[bartender] All right.
-[laughs]
Go for it, go big or go home.
-So, are you from here? Born and raised?
-Yeah.
Born and raised, out on the West Bank,
near Harvey.
-West Bank, best bank, apparently.
-West Bank, best bank.
-Yeah.
-Where are you from?
I'm originally from New York.
Oh, you're from New York, yeah.
-Born and raised.
-Uptown Manhattan.
-Manhattan?
-Yeah.
-I've been to New York.
-Yeah? Where at?
Beaucoup times. Everywhere.
"Beaucoup times." You're definitely, like,
born and raised from here, right?
Born and raised in New Orleans. One
of my craziest adventure's in New York.
-Yeah?
-Got locked up over something I didn't do.
Oh, my goodness. I believe it though.
I got out, but I didn't have my passport.
Everything was in the hotel room.
They broke my phone when they arrested me
'cause they thought--
They got the wrong person.
It's really sad that it happens--
I fit the description
they was looking for. It was crazy.
It was more complex.
I'm just giving you the summary.
It was crazy.
-But I love it--
-You're like, "But that was great."
[chuckles]
There are three cities
in the United States:
New York, New Orleans
and San Francisco.
Everywhere else is Cleveland.
[laughs] Oh, what? That's so random.
Best Tennessee Williams quote.
-[laughs] Have you been to New York?
-[Britton] Yeah, one time.
Me and three of my best friends
made a road trip up to Boston.
-It sounds like a lot of fun.
-It was fun.
This is kind of gross,
but we slept in the vehicle every night.
-You saved coins doing that.
-We didn't have any money.
One of the guys I was with,
he'd get drunk
and piss himself.
-When he falls asleep.
-Oh, no. [groans]
First night of the trip.
Please tell me you guys
we're not in a small car.
-We were--
-Please.
We were... We had a four-way spoon going.
Oh, no, it was worse
than what you would think, yeah.
-It was tight.
-Wow.
-I own a studio now on Freret Street.
-No way.
-I produce, do music, write songs.
-Yeah.
I am a headshot
and commercial photographer.
I'm a doctor. [chuckles] I do anesthesia.
-Wow. Oh, my gosh.
-Yeah, it's been pretty cool.
-This is my--
-Shout out to you.
-Oh.
-That's amazing.
-Thank you. Thank you.
-Oh, my gosh.
Yeah.
Aw, man.
I work for a gutter protection company.
[chuckles]
Gutter protection?
Like, I tell people, like,
"I'm event market manager." "For what?"
"Oh, just... [muffled] gutter protection."
"What was that?" "It's something kind of,
it's not important, but..."
Oh, my gosh, sorry. Like... [laughs]
Uh, listen, I try to make the most fun.
-'Cause I'm very, very goofy.
-Yeah.
-So am I. I'm a clown.
-To be in such a serious--
I'm just trying to be sophisticated
because we just met.
I can't show you the wild side just yet.
[laughs]
You gotta bring it out at dinner. Hmm.
Thank you.
-Cheers, by the way. [chuckles]
-Yeah.
-Cheers.
This is really good.
So what are you doing full-time?
What do you do?
I do a lot.
So right now, like full-time,
I work in digital marketing,
um, for an advertising agency,
and they're based out of Alabama.
Oh, you work from home?
-Mm-hmm. Yeah, I have my own office space.
-I am so jealous.
-I know.
-Ah, that sounds nice.
Honestly, if I'm being honest,
I usually work for my bed or my couch.
-That sounds like the dream.
-But... I know.
And then I do a bunch of,
like, side hustles.
I'm, like, the side hustle queen, so...
-That's what's up.
-...a workaholic.
Yeah, you give me a work opportunity,
and I will choose that over clubbing,
bar hopping, hanging out,
because I love to work so much.
I mean, nothing great comes easy.
You've gotta work.
I try to follow, like,
all the creatives out here.
Go to all the events, and, um...
it's really, really great.
Yeah. Hi.
[waiter] Guys,
your table's ready for you.
-[Demi] Excellent.
-If you just wanna follow me this way.
-Shimmy out of this seat.
-[Trevor laughs]
-All right. Okay.
-It's right this way.
Look at this. This is nice.
I'm kind of feeling a shot.
-Are you down to take a shot?
-A shot?
-Yeah, I'm down to take a shot.
-Why not?
Chilled Jameson shots.
[waiter] Chilled Jameson shots?
All right, guys.
Do you need, like a...
some kind of back to that?
No. I take shots like a champ. [chuckles]
-All right, sounds great.
-[Demi] You'll see.
-So what--
-Don't even make a face and turn.
It's, like, the burn, but I'm, like,
-"Demi, contain yourself. You got this."
-That's what I do. [chuckles]
-Do you have any pets at all?
-I wish. No, I wish.
Growing up, though, I did have
a guinea pig that died out of obesity.
No. I had a guinea pig
when I was small.
And I actually have a, uh,
little pet hedgehog.
[laughing] He is three years old.
So this is my little homie.
He's, uh, Quill Smith.
-Look at this guy. [chuckles]
-Quill Smith.
-Oh, my God.
-[chuckles]
Wait, so is he still this tiny?
Yeah. I think the lifespan is,
like, seven, eight years.
It's my little dude, I love him.
[chuckles]
-Quill Smith. [laughs]
-Yeah. [laughs]
[waiter] Hey, guys. Sorry to interrupt.
Uh, can I get any food going for ya?
[in Spanish] Oh, the pressure.
[Allan in Spanish]
The pressure, do you want me to do it?
-No, wait, let me do it.
-Take your time. It's all right.
The bacon-wrapped pork to start.
[waiter] Awesome, awesome.
The hanger steak fries is calling my name.
-[waiter] All right.
-[Demi] Thank you, appreciate it.
So have you... Have ever been
on a... a blind date before?
I have not ever,
but I have met a couple of people
since I've been here.
The only girl, like, I ever thought
I was gonna marry...
-we-- Yeah, yeah...
-Really?
-It was like that.
-No way. I've never gotten to that point.
It ended terribly.
And ever since then, I don't know,
I've honestly kind of been like disgusted
by the idea of putting myself
out there like that again.
But there's so much, you know...
to lose, especially if, like,
they're not taking it as serious as you.
-You know?
-Yeah.
-But you have dated here?
You were in a relationship here?
No. Let me tell you this.
I had got on, like, on a dating app.
-Oh, for real?
-Yeah.
One of the guys found me on Instagram
and then added me on Instagram.
He initially found you on Tinder,
and looked you up on Instagram?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-He put his work in.
-He crossed a line.
-Yeah, and DM'd me.
Definitely an ax murderer.
-Yes. No, no. Oh.
-[laughs]
Thank God he wasn't.
But when we had finally,
kind of, like, initiated a date,
he offered to pick me up.
'Cause I didn't drive at the time,
and I'm like...
-[Allan] You were a bit weary.
-Yeah.
And you know what I did end up doing?
It's a little embarrassing,
but I brought a butter knife with me.
-'Kay.
-Don't tell me you brought a butter knife.
Believe me. What is a butter knife
'bout to do?
[in Spanish] Oh, my God.
Solid choice.
You didn't have no regular knife?
I just-- I wasn't thinking. I was nervous.
I'm about to meet somebody
that I met online in person.
But it ended up being amazing.
And I was like,
I'm not looking for anything.
Like, I legit just moved here,
I'm just trying to meet people.
And he was like, "I'm not looking
for anything either. Cool."
But like ten months later,
you know, things just escalated.
Like, he even went to New York with me,
met my family...
-Oh, so y'all was legit?
-...and everything.
-Yeah.
-Yes, I thought we were legit.
"You've met my parents,
but you've met all my friends."
"How is this not serious, motherfucker?"
I'm saying, and then,
his feelings never changed,
you know, like, he was still, like,
"I'm not looking for anything,"
then I caught feelings, it happens.
So you were definitely--
You was in love?
-Yeah.
-You fell in love?
-For the first time ever. Ever. Ever.
-Wow. Okay.
[sizzling]
-[waiter] Enjoy.
-Oh, yes.
This looks good.
[waiter] Alright, let me know
if I can grab anything else.
Thank you so much, I appreciate it.
[waiter] Of course.
If I were to get married,
I still don't know how I feel about that.
I've thought about it from time to time,
but like at the same time,
I'm more into finding somebody
I can become their best friend...
-Mm-hmm.
-...and travel well with.
Like, that's all that matters
because you could make 100 grand a year,
but if I've seen 40 countries,
who's rich, who's really rich?
-Amazing. I love that.
-Yeah.
[laughs]
Why not?
To life, 'cause life is to be lived.
-Cheers.
-That's right.
Does it-- Did you end up swallowing
your gum?
Does it still taste like...?
-Does it taste minty?
-I taste my gum.
-Well, even with the fish? [laughs]
-Yeah.
[laughs, sniffles]
What's your favorite thing to do
whenever you have nothing else to do?
-No... No obligations.
-I love music.
Music that makes me move,
since I love to, like, dance.
Same.
I'm very big on, like, Dominican culture.
Culture, you mean...?
-Dominican.
-Oh, okay. Okay.
My parents are from
the Dominican Republic.
-Like, I didn't wanna ask--
-So very heavy-- No, it's fine.
-Might be an asshole thing to do.
-Yeah.
Do you know what bachata is?
Yeah, actually, I dance salsa.
-Do you really?
-[laughs]
Yeah, it's super random,
but I do dance bachata and salsa, yeah.
Get out.
-That is awesome.
-It's little random facts that I just...
That is amazing.
Now, I'm not as good at bachata
as I am at salsa.
It's okay. It's okay.
As long as you can keep rhythm.
-Yeah. I love it.
-Then that's great.
I love that.
Fun fact: I minored in Spanish at LSU.
I would say like I--
I used to be somewhat fluent
-but, I mean, like, you don't...
-Yeah?
Fluent is a strong word.
Now I have to test you.
[sighs] Please...
So if I talk to you in Spanish...
[in Spanish] How do you feel right now?
Ooh.
[in French] I speak Cajun French.
So "I speak French."
The last half I don't know.
Cajun French.
Oh.
Uh... [in Spanish]
You are very interesting.
-[in Spanish] Thank you.
-[in Spanish] And beautiful and pretty.
-[in English] Okay. [chuckles]
-[in English] Let's see. What else...?
How else can I compliment you
with my limited vocabulary?
Oh, no, keep going.
Say everything you can think of. [laughs]
[in Spanish] Very...
Ugly. No ugly!
That would completely, like,
kill everything you just said. [laughs]
Well, I am ready
to keep the party going if you're down.
I'd be honored if you'd, uh,
let me escort you.
Yeah, let's do that.
So, I'm taking my drink with me.
As am I, because it's New Orleans.
-Yes, open container, cheers to that.
-Open containers.
[Demi] Thank you.
-Here you go.
-Yeah.
Watch your step.
These streets are crazy out here.
I know.
[Zach] Watch your step right here.
-Thank you.
-Yeah. [chuckles]
[Demi] In the beginning, I had you
played out as, like, this bad boy...
-Me?
-...image. Yes. [chuckles]
It's more of the confidence
that you have, and stuff.
It's just the way, like,
you carry yourself.
And I was like, this guy is a bad boy.
But you don't seem like it at all.
No. I'm from New Orleans.
-We all carry a certain confidence.
-Yes.
[Allan] Such a dope city.
First blind date...
-[chuckles] Ever.
-...could've gone a lot worse.
Yes. No, that is absolutely true.
It could've been, like,
awkward from the get.
But I don't think it was,
so I'm happy about that.
Oh, my gosh, look at these decorations.
Watch out for that.
-Ooh, yeah. [chuckles]
-Watch out for that.
You're busy looking at the decorations,
-I'm looking at the hazards here.
-I know. Next thing I'll poke my eye out.
Yeah, don't do that. That's...
That would totally ruin the entire night,
and maybe the rest of your life.
See, that's why I'm here. I'm here,
so that you don't walk into those things.
[chuckles] Yes.
Watch out for this car.
Chilly.
You're good.
[Noel] Let's see.
Let's do weight on the back foot,
and then put right hand on the hip.
Oh, okay.
There you go, then flare
that shoulder out toward me.
This shoulder?
Just like that
and then look up at that light.
Oh, okay, all right.
Oh, wow, I think this is gonna look good.
Fart nuggets.
What? [laughs]
Bingo, told you.
[exhales] Did you say fart nuggets?
That's exactly what I said,
and it worked too.
[Demi] I am curious to see
some of your moves.
[Zach] Where's the music at?
[Demi] We got this.
-I wanna see some of your salsa moves.
-There's two... There's obviously...
-There's two versions.
-So I only know basics.
So, the first thing you wanna do
is move your foot back.
So it's one, two, three...
five, six, seven.
Stop for a second.
Don't let me fall.
-Feel that tension. Okay.
-Yes.
As long as you have that tension
and you have the feet going,
I can pretty much do whatever I want.
-And, like, it's easy.
-But I should...
But I should pretty much,
like, stay in place?
Yeah, like, you're walking
in a straight line.
So you're always the princess,
you're walking straight back and forth
all the time and I'm moving around you,
and I'm making things happen
no matter what.
-Okay.
-Right?
So, you're just, kind of, like, make,
you're just...
-Okay.
-I'm right here, right?
Like, I can have you walk
in a straight line
-and then you spin. [laughs]
-Okay.
That's all it takes, right?
-It's a little bit of footwork and then--
-Oh, that was good. I'm sweating.
It's like I had an entire salsa lesson.
You taught me something.
I appreciate it.
You gotta be tough here.
You gotta have a little bad boy in you,
I think, to succeed.
Okay, so at least I wasn't wrong.
At least I wasn't wrong.
[Allan]
I think I've got a little bit in me.
[Demi] A little bit naturally though.
-My mama raised me right.
-Look at your--
[indistinct] [both chuckle]
[Demi] But I know I'm, like, thankfully
I know how to walk in heels
even a little tipsy.
[honking]
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
All right.
Oh, man.
I honestly didn't know what to expect...
-Me neither.
-...at all.
But I am having...
Like for real, I'm having a great time.
Yeah, no, me too,
even though this is
completely nerve-wracking.
Have you ever been on a blind date?
Did your parents ever try to,
like, set you up?
Nope. This is, like, this is it.
I find it pretty intriguing and fun
because you already, like,
kind of know what's coming.
You, like, research to try to figure out
who this person is.
But when you don't it's, like, you're just
going in, it's, hey, it's on a whim.
When you do date... research,
you do research?
-Yeah, definitely. You have to figure--
-Background checks. [laughs]
You have to... [laughs]
Friends in the FBI,
"Hey, can you just do a quick, uh--
I'll buy you dinner,
just if you can quickly..."
-"Can you check out this girl? I gotta--"
-"They did what?
-How long ago was that?" [laughs]
-Oh, my God.
[laughs]
[Demi] Oh, this is my favorite one.
It's right after I made you laugh
with fart nuggets.
-Fart nuggets.
-That's the one, yeah.
-I'm gonna always remember that.
-Yeah, remember that one. Take it in--
-But I love this one.
-Remember it forever.
And you can use it too,
use it whenever you want.
Yeah, I appreciate it.
I want my studio to get up and running
to the best ability it can go.
There we go, a bad boy with...
with ambition. [chuckles]
I ain't that bad.
With ambition and nice eyes.
Oh, sh--. Oh, yeah. [laughs]
[indistinct]
-Do you want kids in this lifetime?
-[Britton] So...
-Go ahead.
-[chuckles] I don't know.
I get a lot of pressure from my mom.
My mom is like...
like, "When are you gonna settle down,
get married, have kids?"
Right now, I say I don't want kids.
I feel like you would make some
cute babies, though, if I'm being honest.
[laughs] I appreciate that.
I have thought about it,
but I have so many goals for myself,
like, with my career, that I'm, like,
"Am I gonna be that mom
that just wants to work all the time?"
Hey, dude, I'll be a stay-at-home dad.
Just let me know.
[chuckles]
I feel like sometimes you,
like, have your guard up or maybe--
I do. I guess it's just--
Do you feel with me
you have your guard up in a sense?
-Absolutely.
-Absolutely. I feel that. I get that vibe.
And not, like, purposely,
because, you know,
you are very, like, nice
and very respectful.
Just past situations.
Do I remind you of someone
in a past situation?
Obviously there's tons of things
I don't know.
In general, I feel like I have...
given in too easily to the point
where I got taken advantage of.
-One hundred percent.
-And it's our first time meeting, so--
But I am intrigued to see, like,
-where this goes from here.
-That's reasonable.
Yeah.
You're cool as hell. You're fine as hell.
You're cool as hell.
Thank you. Thank you. I appreciate that.
-But I am...
-It's that time?
...exhausted. Yes, it is.
It is getting late. I mean...
-Yeah.
-I think I'm gonna...
Head out. Yep.
Britton.
-Demi.
-[chuckles]
All right, I will see you.
Bye.
[Trevor] Get home safe.
[Demi]
Would you mind if we, like, share a Lyft?
-One hundred percent.
-Let's do it.
So, now that you've had this experience,
would you go on a blind date again?
-I'd definitely go on a blind date.
-Not that anybody could top me.
-Because I think, you know, it was great.
-Yeah, I know...
I'm thinking, blind date,
as long as you're the girl,
sounds good to me.
[both laughing]
I would say I'm almost like
a hopeless romantic.
-Well, you're in good company because...
-Yeah, absolutely.
...self-confessed hopeless romantic
right here.
Yeah? Oh, that's awesome.
I usually work 8:00 to 4:00.
For real?
-My bad. [chuckles]
-No, it's fine.
-I ain't trying to keep you all night.
-No, I'm good.
I'm chilling, I'm good.
-Good.
-It's good.
Yeah, it was a good night.
That's a great night.
-Definitely.
-Right.
It's really funny that we've never...
run into each other.
I mean, it was meant to be not to.
-Until now.
-Right? Until this point.
-One hundred percent.
-[laughs]
We're definitely
gonna have to exchange information.
All right, contacts.
-All right, this is you.
-Great to meet you.
I'm gonna... I'll text you.
It's me, your girl.
[chuckles]
-Demi Diaz.
-You bet.
It was great meeting you.
-Great meeting you too.
-Bye. Yes.
-Get home safe.
-Could I perhaps have a good night kiss?
I actually don't kiss on the first date.
So I will-- I will leave you
anticipating for more.
I actually like that better.
Yes, awesome.
I hope you have a good night.
Bye. [chuckles] Bye. Have a good night.
You too.
[car door closes]
[chuckles]
Oh, my gosh.
-Great.
-Well, this is you. This was so much fun.
Thank you so much.
I appreciate the date.
It was very, very nice meeting you.
-It was great meeting you.
-Bye.
-Bye. [groans]
Till... Till next time.
-I got you. One more time.
-All right.
-Bye.
-See you. Bye.
-Dale.
["Holy Water" by
Anjulie & Natalia Lafourcade playing]
♪ I know you’re begging and pleading ♪
♪ Baby, you can’t hide ♪
♪ Deep down your broken and bleeding ♪
♪ Barely alive ♪
♪ Let me give you that holy water... ♪
What's up, girl? [laughing]
How you doing?
I'm good. How are you?
Doing great.
Good to see you.
[both laughing]
It's a little windy out here today.
[Demi] Yeah, it is.
-[Zach] Definitely get a drink.
-Yeah.
[Zach] I was thinking,
a bit of salsa.
Pick up where we left off, right?
Right, and we're right near Bourbon,
so it's omens. We could do it.
Shots, then, shots and salsa.
-Chilled.
-Chilled, shots and salsa.
♪ Let me give you that holy water ♪
♪ See, I just wanna lift you from below ♪
♪ You know you love it
When I give you what you want ♪
♪ Let me give you that holy water ♪
♪ Dripping down... Dripping down...
Dripping down... ♪